

## Thomas Pritchard

Game & Product Designer

Email
Portfolio
Twitter
GitHub

hi@tpritc.com www.tpritc.com twitter.com/tpritc github.com/tpritc

Profile

I'm Thomas, a Game & Product Designer with a passion for designing and building delightful experiences for players and users alike. I use my skills, developed while working with a multitude of startups and existing companies as a design consultant, to help build new products, and develop existing ones.

Experience

Game Designer at Field Tested (Hereford, UK) - January 2017 to Present

As co-founder at Field Tested, I have had to wear a number of hats. From software developer to public relations, I've led the design, development, and publishing of Colourise, a virtual reality puzzle game for SteamVR. Colourise was released in April 2017 to a positive response.

Product Designer at Developer Town (Indianapolis, USA) – January 2014 to Present

As a designer, specialising in user experience, at DeveloperTown, I worked closely with clients to help them realise their products at their most critical time: ideation and initial design. I did user research, created personas, task flows, wireframes, and visual designs that scaled from a smartphone to a large desktop monitor. So far with DeveloperTown I have helped bring seven products from idea, through design, iteration, marketing, and build, to market.

Product Designer at Old St Labs (*London*, *UK*) – June 2016 to December 2016

As designer number two at Old St Labs, I helped refine the look and feel of their premier product, Vizibl, in its infancy. I was led efforts to use user data to inform design decisions, using analytics to make choices that helped us optimise product direction and improve engagement.

Education

BSc Computer Science at Plymouth University – September 2012 to June 2016 First Class Degree in Computer Science, with honours.

Skills

- User Research & Prototyping (InVision, Paper Prototypes, Writing Scripts, Personas)
- Task Flows & Wireframing (Sketch)
- Visual Design (Sketch, Adobe Photoshop)
- Front-End Web Design (HTML, Haml, CSS & Sass, Javascript)
- macOS & iOS Software Development (Swift, Cocoa)
- Game Design & Development (Unity, C#)